welcome to the me around boot camp I'm T
I'm chub and today we're having a
product review product review another
new product review okay so I know not a
new product just a new review right got
a few comments when I brought in the
office well where people are like how do
you smoke in your office in ORS County
you know right and uh great question and
at first I just started smoking there
deci see if anybody would call me out
literally my first exhale it wasn't 20
minutes later you take your first hit do
you remember what you're smoking
uh I it was something that you gave me
but I I can't remember exactly what it
was definitely stunk then yeah yeah oh
yeah so what happened I I I took a nice
nice rip uh
exhaled and you know 20 minutes later I
got a phone call from the landlord like
what the [\h__\h] are you doing is the
landlord on site no that makes worse
somebody got somebody got I rate and
called
him and I don't day one this is 20 I'm
just like yes I my first office I am
like so awesome me get my out let me
celebrate yeah like this is what I've
always wanted to do have my own office
and you're doing it you're doing it boom
backed out of reality real fast you know
so what he tell you so he's like you're
not doing that again promise me he'll
never smoke in that off kick you out I
have to kick you out he doesn't want to
kick me out cuz you know not
allow yeah so solution to the issue what
do we have smoke buddy smoke buddy and
uh man I can't it looks weird what do
you think this looks like man it looks
like something that goes on a paintball
gun so it's a device that you use to
blow smoke through I what I'm guessing
is there's a nice SL ccle filter right
here okay and you
just I'm I've got this thing stuffed
right here oh man I really so I really
wanted to bring this I'm going to lung
bleed it right here yeah yeah so so when
I exhale through through this thing uh
you if if you do it slowly you really
don't see any smoke coming out Zer none
none at all so I want to see but your
size now when you're saying when you
exhale is there instructions that come
with this no so you're able not that I
got it I got this as a gift so let's see
if it works CHS
that's why you're here to do these very
important
tests this is going to be a very very
good challenge for the smoke buddy it
also comes with this cute little
figurine this is an average hit this
isn't even a big hit
okay and I'm seeing absolutely nothing
coming out of that just nothing I
exhaled there's a little bit that comes
back out the top there yeah you got to
really pull through that last there you
go H interesting I think there's a
little bit of user error on the this
being my first time ever using it right
so I'm going to give it another shot for
sure okay I want to do a big ass hit
okay all right so this is smoke budy
test part two Chubs is going to take a
huge monster rib and see if the smoke
buddy will work that bowl as stuffed as
I can get it wow ice is nice ice is nice
all right here we go uh smoke buddy test
uh part
two it's really cool to watch the smoke
fill up the
perks especially on this
p and this is going to be a epic
R oh
B nothing nothing
that's almost amazing nothing came out
of that
CHS now if you cap
it nothing out of there either God my
breast
smells no it's it's this side smells
like carbon this my this side's a little
funky yeah yeah that was kind of gross
but you know got to test it um five out
of five four and a half out of five it
would be a five if there was a way to
have the the the extra smoke yeah not
not have to take a second breath to push
it
through
4.75 I mean that's that's a pretty damn
good product right here smoke budy if
you guys ever need to smoke Incognito
and you're worried about
exhaling I just blew a big ass bonger
through this and not an iota of smoke
came out so I like it for the boot camp
I'm tag I'm chub peace peace